- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_12
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: DarkMatter
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Yash_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT5
  ItemRewardQty: 15.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Phaeris_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: HoningStoneT5
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Morgaine_04
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT5
  ItemRewardQty: 15.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Sun_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: DarkMatter
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_04
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: earringshatteredmountainT5
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_alt
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_alt_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: DarkMatter
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Russo_06
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT5
  ItemRewardQty: 15.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99G_Grace_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_65
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Headgear_65
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_destroyer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Warmonger
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_destroyer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_musketeer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Musketeer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_musketeer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_mystic
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Theurgist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_mystic
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_occultist
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Occultist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_occultist
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_ranger
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Tracker
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_ranger
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_soldier
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Mercenary
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_soldier
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_swordsman
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_swordsman
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99G_MSQ_SM_DesertVector
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99G_MSQ_SM_DesertVector_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1625_Ghazi_p1
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99G_MSQ_13
  RequiredAchievementId: 99G_MSQ_12
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99G_MSQ_SM_DesertVector_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: DarkMatter
  ItemRewardQty: 200.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_title"
  Description: "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
